<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AT Android Seminar Topic</title>
    <link>https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AT Android Seminar Topic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tổng quan sơ lược firebase</title>
      <link>https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/t%E1%BB%95ng-quan-s%C6%A1-l%C6%B0%E1%BB%A3c-firebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/t%E1%BB%95ng-quan-s%C6%A1-l%C6%B0%E1%BB%A3c-firebase/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Firebase là một nền tảng di động giúp bạn nhanh chóng phát triển các ứng dụng chất lượng cao, phát triển ứng dụng cho người dùng quy mô lớn và kiếm được nhiều tiền hơn. (Firebase gives you the tools to develop high-quality apps, grow your user base, and earn more money. We cover the essentials so you can monetize your business and focus on your users.)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akaj-team.github.io/seminar-topic/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper  Hugo is ideal for blogs, corporate websites, creative portfolios, online magazines, single page applications or even a website with thousands of pages.
Hugo is for people who want to hand code their own website without worrying about setting up complicated runtimes, dependencies and databases.
Websites built with Hugo are extremelly fast, secure and can be deployed anywhere including, AWS, GitHub Pages, Heroku, Netlify and any other hosting provider.
Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>